We're millions of Muslims around the world fast, not only from material sustenance, fast, not only from material sustenance, fast, we have attorneys, we have attorneys, please leave our house, you are guests at our house, this is our first amendment, this is our first amendment, it is, the National Lawyers Guild has informed this is our first amendment, right, and they are.
So I'm coming off my Instagram break to just speak to this situation right here because I see a lot of conjecture in the comments, one, this woman had an event at her house for the university, so basically you are using your house as a university event, your house becomes an extension of the university, so the laws of the university apply to your house, hence why the young lady was saying, this is our first amendment, right?
Second, even if it wasn't attached to university, if you invite someone to your house and they say something you don't like, the best thing you can do is invite them to leave, if they do not leave, you can call the police for trespassing, you cannot put your hands on them, you cannot put your hands on people,
and this is something that white people seem to really think is okay, whether it's snatching someone's phone or touching someone's hair without asking them, you cannot put your hands on people,
and if you do, there should be consequences, and that's just really the reality that you take, listen, there's some people that my hands might very well end up on,
and I know that there are consequences that attach to that, but the reality in this situation is that this young lady was invited to the event, I want to make that clear,
she was invited to the event, she was speaking about Palestine as she was speaking about the end of Ramadan and how Palestinians were experiencing Ramadan and experiencing Eid,
and this woman and her husband became so irate, but here's the sweetest, most bittersweet part of all of this,
it's my house, so you get it, so you get it, you get what it means to be in your house and have someone come into your house
and saying what they want to say and you not being okay with that, imagine if they were coming into your house
and saying they're going to stay and that you have no choice but to be okay with that, so you get it.